[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the first movie for the Olsen twins?", "correct_answer": "Little Rascals", "incorrect_answers": ["Little Man", "The Wizard", "Going Overboard"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What term means fear of accidents?", "correct_answer": "Dystychiphobia", "incorrect_answers": ["Dentophobia", "Dikephobia", "Dendrophobia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "General Electric, one of the worlds biggest corporations, is active in many market segments. In which of these areas do they NOT operate?", "correct_answer": "oil drilling", "incorrect_answers": ["finance", "electricity", "jet engines"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the oldest brewery in the USA that is still operating?", "correct_answer": "Yuengling", "incorrect_answers": ["Brooklyn Brewery", "Sierra Nevada Brewery", "Boston Beer Company"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the prevalent language in Central America?", "correct_answer": "Spanish", "incorrect_answers": ["French", "English", "Mayan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The stewardess in the film The Big Bus, played by Stockard Channing, nearly died in what way?", "correct_answer": "drowning in a room filled with soft drinks", "incorrect_answers": ["being crushed by a flying spare tire", "None of these", "being sucked into a handicapped toilet"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "To whom did the butler confess that he had kidnapped the cats in The Aristocats?", "correct_answer": "Frou Frou the horse", "incorrect_answers": ["Abigail the goose", "Georges the lawyer", "Madame Bonfamille the retired opera singer"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which former Yugoslavian republic was the first to be admitted to the European Union?", "correct_answer": "Slovenia", "incorrect_answers": ["Macedonia", "Serbia", "Croatia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What terrifying accident happened to the assistant director Jan Michelini, and later to actor James Caviezel, during the filming of the 2004 movie The Passion Of The Christ?", "correct_answer": "They were struck by lightning.", "incorrect_answers": ["They got bitten by a snake.", "They nearly lost a finger.", "They fell of a cliff."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The coat of arms of which country includes a depiction of a cactus?", "correct_answer": "Mexico", "incorrect_answers": ["Brasil", "Peru", "Guatemala"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which is greater: the circumference of Earth from pole to pole or the circumference of Earth around the equator?", "correct_answer": "The equatorial circumference", "incorrect_answers": ["The polar circumference", "None of these", "They are equal"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the occupation of The Greatest American Hero, according to the TV show?", "correct_answer": "High school teacher", "incorrect_answers": ["Police officer", "Taxi driver", "Deep diver"]}]